Guide to the Andrews Memorial Bookplate Collection of Irene D. Andrews Pace (School and College Bookplates)
Yale University Arts Library
- Bookplates
  - L – R (Box 3, Folder 18-25)
    - R. K. Universiteit Te Nijmegen, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      G. M. Pot. Van Regteren Altena
    - Richard Platt's Grammar School, Aldenham, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rocca S. Casciano, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rochdale Parochial Grammar School, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rochester Athenaeum and Mechanics Institute Library (now Rochester Institute of Technology), undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rochester City Normal School, Rochester, NY, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      G. E. Botsford, artist
    - Romania Convent, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      Irene Holzer-Weinek, artist
    - Roosevelt College, Chicago, IL, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rotterdam Ambachts School, Rotterdam, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      Th. Haanebrink, artist
    - Rotherham College, 1879 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Roxbury Latin School, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Royal College of Dental Surgeons, Ontario, Canada, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Royal Dungannon School, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Royal Grammar School, Lancaster, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Royal Holloway College, University of London, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Royal Hungarian University (now Corvinus University), undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      F. A. (of Budapest), artist
    - Royal Military College, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Roycemore School, Evanston, IL, undated; 1; letters (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rugbirns School, Rugby, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rugby School, Rugby, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      O. Jewitt, artist
    - Rutgers Female Institute, Rutgers University, NY, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      Forde, artist
  - S – T (Box 4, Folder 26-28)
    - Sacre Coeur, Malvern, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Adrian Feint, artist
    - Sacre Coeur de Jesus, Torino, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Sacred Heart School of Education, Fall River, MA, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Albans Diocesan Training Institution for Schoolmistresses, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint Augustine's College, Canterbury, England, UK, undated; 4 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Augustine Monastery, Ramsgate, Kent, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Bede's College, Manchester, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint Benedict, Fort Augustus, Scotland, undated; 4 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint Benedict (Sancti Benedicti Floriacensis), undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Catharine's College Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, 1700; 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Colman's College, Fermoy, Co. Cork, Ireland, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - S. Donati, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint. Edmund College, University of Oxford, UK, undated; 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Edward's School, St. Francis, Oxford, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St Francis (S. Francisci Conv. Lucernae), undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Georges School, Newport, RI, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Gregory's College, undated; 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Gregory Monastery Library, Downside, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Gregory's College, Portsmouth, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Gregory's School, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Hendriks College, Belgium, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Luc De Jaegher, artist
    - St. Hilda's Hall, Oxford, University of Oxford, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint James's, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Collegium Sancti Johannis Evangelistae in academia Cantabrigiensi, undated; 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint John's College Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. John's College Library, Annapolis, MD, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint John's College Oxford, University of Oxford, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Lawrence's Students Lower Library, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Maries College, Rugby, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Sanctae Mariae de Oscott College, Sutton Coldfield, England, UK, undated; 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St Mary's Dominican High School, New Orleans, LA, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint Mary of the Wasatch, Salt Lake City, UT, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint Mary's School Library, Raleigh, NC, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Mark's School, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Mark's School Library, Southborough, MA, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Matthew School, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Paligian, artist
    - Saint Paul Academy, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Jerome Hill, artist
    - St. Paul's School, Oxford, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Paul's School Library, undated; 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Saint Peter's College, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      H. J. J. Badeley, artist
    - St. Peter's School, Cambridge, New Zealand, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Scholastica Academy, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Stephen's Green, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Vincent College, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - St. Wilfrid, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Salem Massachusetts State Normal School, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Salop Archidiaconal, Ipswich, England, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Cowell's Anastatic Press, artist
    - Sandhill Farm School, North Carolina, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      P. O. Palmstron
    - San Fausto de Campcentellas Escuelas Nacionales, Spain, undated; 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Santa Barbara State College, University of California, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      E. F., artist
    - Sarah Ainsworth Rogers, Smith College, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      H. L. S., artist
    - Sarum Theological College, Salisbury, Wiltshire, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Schenectady High School, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Viola Stetson, artist
    - Schola Feinaigliana, Dublin, Ireland, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Holbrooke, artist
    - Scholae Collinae Molinensis, 1834 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Schola Grammatica Plumptonensis, Plumpton, North Yorkshire, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Scholae Hackneiensis, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Schol. Reg. Petriburg, The Kings School, Peterborough, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Schol. Regal. Shirburn, Watlington, Oxfordshire, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - School Library, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - School Voor Ziekenoppasters, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Ant. Rousseau, artist
    - Schuylkill College Library, Pennsylvania (no longer in existence), undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Scripps College, Claremont, CA, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Scripps College, Claremont, CA, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Harry Marvin French, artist
    - Selwyn College Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Seminaire, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Seminarii Willibaldini EystadiiÎ, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Seminarium Segusinum, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Seminary for General Education, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      F. Green, artist
    - Seton Hall College, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Shady Side Academy, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Shrewsbury School Library, Shrewsbury, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Shirburn Regal School, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Shurtleff College Library, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Sidney Cooper School of Art, Canterbury, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      M. Caldwell, artist
    - Sidney Sussex College, Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, 1701; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Siena College, Loudonville, NY, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Sion College Library, London, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Sion College Library, London, England, UK, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      J. F. Badeley, artist
    - Simmons College Library, Boston, MA, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Sir John Cass Technical Institute, London Metropolitan University, UK, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Sisters of St. John the Divine Convent Library, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Skidmore College, Saratoga Springs NY, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Slovenska Universita v Bratislave, Slovakia, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Karel Frech, artist
    - Smith College, undated; 10 items (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Smith College, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Snell Seminary, Oakland, CA, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Solihull Grammar School (now Solihull School), Solihull, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Somersetshire College, Bath, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Somerville College, Oxford, University of Oxford, UK, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Sostene Convents, 1889 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Southern Methodist University, Dallas, TX, undated; 4 items (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - South Wales and Monmouthshire University College, Lampeter, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Southwestern College, Memphis, TN, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Spring Hill College, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Springfield High School, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Stadium High School, California, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Stains Monastery, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - State College of Washington, Washington University, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - State School for Education of Children, Hof Oberkirch, Bavaria, Germany, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - State Teachers College, Millersville, PA, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Burl Osborn, artist
    - State University of New Mexico, Albuquerque, NM, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - State University Utrecht, Netherlands, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Stepny College, 1810 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - St. John's College Library, Annapolis, MD, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Stockholms Hogskolas, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Suomen Koneliike Oy, Finland, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Alf. Danning (of Helsinki), artist
    - Svenska Nobel Akademiens, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Swarthmore College, Pennsylvania, 1927; 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Swarthmore College Library, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Sweet Briar College, undated; 1 letter (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Sydenham College, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Sydney Teachers' College, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
      R. D., artist
    - Tavistock Grammar School, Devonshire, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Teachers College, New York City, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
      LaMont A. Warner, artist
    - Technological High School, Atlanta, GA, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Gymnasium Te Alkmaar, Netherlands, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Texas Technological College, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      C. L. S., artist; R. W. D., artist
    - Theresianischen Akadmie in Wien, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Tilley House Academy, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Harris & Co., artist
    - Timaru Toys' High School, South Canterbury, New Zealand, undated; 3 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Watts Rule Torino, artist
    - Toronto Normal School Library, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Toynbee Hall Library, East London, England, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Trinity College Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 27 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Trinity College, Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
      E. W., artist
    - Trinity College, Cambridge, Universtiy of Cambridge, UK, 1740; 5 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      W. Stephenson, artist
    - Trinity College, Dublin, undated; 16 items (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Trinity College, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Trinity House, undated; 4 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Tufts College Div. Sch., Tufts University, Boston, MA, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Tufts College, Tufts University, Boston, MA, undated; 2 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Tufts College, Tufts University, Boston, MA, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Tulane Univ. Medical School, Louisiana, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      E. J. Palfrey, artist
    - Tunbridge School Library, undated; 5 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - U – Y, undated (Box 5, Folder 29-36)
    - Union Free School, Chatham, NY, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Union Theological Seminary, New York, NY, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - United Presbyterian Library, Edinburgh, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Universidade de Sao Paulo, Brazil, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Universite de France, Dieppe, France, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - L'Universite, undated; 4 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University College, London, England, UK, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University College School, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University College School, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University Corr. Coll, Burlington House, Cambridge, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University Correspondence School, Cambridge, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University of Alabama, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
      C. V. Kirby, artist
    - University of Aberdeen, Aberdeen, Scotland, UK, undated; 22 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University of Baltimore, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University of Bombay (now Mumbai), undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Cecil L. Burns, artist
    - University of Bucharest, Romania, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
      J. V. Socecu, artist
    - University of California (authority records before 1866-1952), undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University of California, undated; 7 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      A. R. W., artist
    - University of California, undated; 13 items (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, undated; 30 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Bill Bellin, artist
    - University of Cambridge, Cambridge, England, UK, undated; 11 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Cambridge, Cambridge, England, UK, 1736; 4 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      J. Pine, artist
    - University of Cape Town, South Africa, undated; 1 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Chicago, Illinois, undated; 12 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Cincinnati, Ohio, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Conimaric, undated; 4 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Krakow (or Jagellonian University), Krakow, Poland, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Edinburgh, Edinburgh, Scotland, UK, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Hawaii, Honolulu, HI, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Houston, undated; 1; bookplate (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Illinois, undated; s items (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Illinois, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
      W. G. Ratter, artist
    - University of Iowa (earlier State University of Iowa), undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Ireland, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Leeds, Leeds, England, UK, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Louisville, KY, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Ainslie Hewett, artist
    - University of Louisville, KY, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
      B. W. Alberts, artist
    - University of Maine at Orono, ME, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Maryland, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Michigan, undated; 7 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Michigan, undated; 4 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      E. F. Faber, artist
    - University of Michigan, 1931-32; 9 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      W. H. N. Bicknell, artist
    - University of Michoacan, Mexico, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - University of Minnesota, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Missouri, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Nebraska, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - New York University, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - New York University, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Edith Nankivell, artist
    - New York University, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Sprague, artist
    - University of North Carolina, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Notre Dame, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Oxford, Oxford, England, UK, 1760; 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Oxford, Oxford, England, UK, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Clements, artist
    - University of Pennsylvania Laboratory of Dermatological Research, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Pennsylvania, undated; 16 items (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Pittsburgh, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Puerto Rico, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Rochester, NY, undated; 5 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Philip Merz, T. T. Swinburen, and Joseph Thuringer, artists
    - University of Rochester, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      E. B. Bird, artist
    - University of Rochester, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Myron Smith, artist
    - University of Rochester, 1915; 4 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Laurence Kennedy, artist
    - University of Rochester, undated; 27 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Rochester, undated; 5 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Claude Bragdon, artist; Philipp Merz, artist
    - University of Rochester, Du Bois Press, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Philipp Merz, artist
    - University of Rochester, undated; 4 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Rochester, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Claude Bragdon, artist; Louis Jacobs, lettering
    - University of Rochester, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Rockwell Kent, Claude Bragdon, and Lawrence Kennedy, artists
    - University of Rome, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      G. D. T., artist
    - University of Southern California, undated; 13 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Southern California, undated; 4 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Dreka, artist; Brasz, artist
    - University of St. Andrews, St. Andrews, Fife, Scotland, UK, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Tennessee at Chattanooga, undated; 5 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Texas, Austin, undated; 1 bookplate, 1 letter, 1 pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of the South, Sewanee, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Arthur H. Noll, artist
    - University of Toronto, Ontario, Canada, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Utah, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Vermont and State Agricultural College, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Washington, undated; 4 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Wisconsin, Madison, undated; 7 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Wisconsin, Madison, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
      M. Breese, artist
    - University of theWitwatersrand, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - U. S. Grant High School, Los Angeles, CA, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Vassar College, NY, 1902; 2 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      R. R. Gentry, artist; C. C. Nobel, artist
    - Vassar College, NY, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Vassar College, NY, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      W. F. Hopson, artist
    - Vassar College, NY, undated; 1; bookplate (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Ralph M. Pearson, artist
    - Vassar College, NY, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      A. H. Noll, artist
    - Vasco da Gama College, Portugal, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Vermont Episcopal Institute Library, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Wake Forest College, North Carolina, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      L. M. Patten, artist
    - Wake Forest College, North Carolina, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
      F. C. Blank, artist
    - Wall School, Dublin, Ireland, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Warren High School Library, Broken Bow, OK, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Rockwell Kent, artist
    - Warszawie Ksiegozbior Instytut, Warsaw, Poland, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      K. Wiszniewski, artist
    - Washington College (later Washington and Jefferson College), Pennysylvania, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Washington College of Law, American University, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      T. G., artist
    - Washington State College, University of Vermont, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Wellesley College, MA, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      G. E. Johnson, artist
    - Wellesley College, MA, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Agnes Abbot, artist
    - Wellesley College, MA, undated; 8 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Wellington College, Crowthorne, Berkshire, UK, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Wells College, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Wells Diocesan College, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Clements, sc.; Russell, del.
    - Wells Theological College, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Wesleyan University, Middletown, CT, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Western College for Women, Oxford, OH, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Westfield High School, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - West High Scholl, Rochester, NY, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Zella Hale Webster, artist
    - Western Reserve Academy (later moved to Cleveland, OH, as Adelbert College), 1826-1882 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Western Reserve University (now Case Western University), undated; 8 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Westminster College Cambridge, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      A. Wyon, artist
    - Westminster College, New Wilmington, PA, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Westminster College of Music, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Westminster College of Toronto, University of Ontario, Canada, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Westminster French Charity School, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Westminster School, London, England, UK, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - W.H. Regin. Coll. Cantab, Cambridge, England, UK, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Wigan Grammar School, Greater Manchester, UK, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      J. H. Le Keux, sc.; W. Rigg, del.
    - Willamette University, Salem, OR, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Dean Pollock, artist
    - William Jewel College, Liberty, MO, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Williams College, Williamstown, MA, undated; 5 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Wm. Mann Co., artist
    - Williams College, Williamstown, MA, undated; 8 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Williams College, Williamstown, MA, undated; 6 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      J. B Daniels, artist
    - Williams College Library, Williamstown, MA, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Francis I. Smith, artist
    - Wilmington College, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Wilmington Institute, Wilmington, DE, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Wilmington High School, Wilmington, OH, undated; 1; bookplate (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Winchester, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Winchester College, (Winton College, Collegium B. Mariae), Winchester, England, UK, 1740; 4 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Winthrop Normal and Industrial College of North Carolina, Rock Hill, SC, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology (Philadelphia?), undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Woburn Abbey, Bedfordshire, England, UK, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Worcester Academy, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Worcester Polytechnic Institute, Worcester, MA, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Worcester Polytechnic Institute Worcester, MA, 1926; 2 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      R. G. de la Mater, artist
    - Wycombe Abbey School, High Wycombe, England, UK, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Yale College, Yale University, New Haven, CT, undated; 6 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Yale Law Library, Yale University, New Haven, CT, undated; 3 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Yale Medical Library, Yale University, New Haven, CT, undated; 2 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Yale University, New Haven, CT, undated; 95 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Yale University Library, Yale University, New Haven, CT, 1901; 4 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Yale University Library, New Haven, CT, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)